Do you realize this is probably the last
time we're all going to be here in
the coffee house?
As six single people?
What?
What's happening to the coffee house?
Oh, okay.
Yep, from now on it's going to be
the four of you guys and me and
the missus.
The little woman, the wife, the old ball
and chain.
Old?
The young, hot ball and chain.
I'm head to go.
Oh, we gotta go.
Oh, where are you guys going?
We're going to pick up the wedding dress
and then we're going to have lunch with
mom.
Joey, you're having lunch with my mom?
No, I just heard lunch.
Yeah, I can go.
Sure.
Actually, I'm kind of glad they're leaving because
I need to talk to you about something.
What's up?
Well, this may be a little awkward.
Listen, if you want to borrow money, it's
kind of a bad time.
I'm buying dinner for 128 people tomorrow night.
It's not that.
Now, what I'm going to say to you,
I'm not saying this as your friend, okay?
I'm saying it as Monica's older brother.
But you're still my friend.
Not for the next few minutes.
During this time?
Are you still my best man?
Nope.
Do I still call you Ross?
Okay.
You guys are getting married tomorrow and I
couldn't be more thrilled for both of you.
But as Monica's older brother, I have to
tell you this.
If you ever hurt my little sister, if
you ever cause her any unhappiness of any
kind, I will hunt you down and kick
your ass.
What?
I'm serious.
Okay, dude, stop it, okay?
I'm not kidding here.
Hey, I hear what you're saying, okay?
And thanks for the warning.
No problem.
So, are we friends again?
Yeah.
You won't believe what Monica's older brother just
said to me.
Knock, knock, knock.
What you doing, hon?
I'm making a list of all the things
that are most likely to go wrong at
the wedding.
That way I can be prepared.
What are they?
Well, so far I have my bridesmaid's dresses
won't get picked up, my veil gets lost,
or I don't have my something blue.
Hey, those are all the things that I'm
responsible for.
I have to go with the odds, Rach.
Hey, you guys.
Remember that audition I had a while ago
and I didn't get the part?
The commercial?
No.
That play?
That other play?
No.
The movie?
Yes!
Oh, the one with the pilot and his
dog who flies planes?
No, no, but man, that one hurt.
No, this is the one about the soldiers
who fight in World War I.
Oh, yeah.
Back then, you know, we called it the
Great War.
It really was.
Well, anyway, the guy they wanted backed out
and now they want me.
I start shooting today.
Congratulations!
Wait, wait, wait, you can't start today.
Today is the rehearsal dinner.
Oh, no, I'll be done by then.
Oh.
Well, then way to go, you big movie
star.
I know.
All right, I'll see you guys over there.
I'm off to fight the Nazis.
Oh, wait, Joey.
We fought the Nazis in World War II,
not World War I.
Whoa, okay.
Yeah, well, who was in World War I?
Go ahead.
Don't be late.
Go, go.
Go.
Who did we fight in World War I?
Mexico?
Yes.
Very good.
Hey, Joey, we're ready.
Yeah, me too.
Richard, we're ready for you.
Joey Tribbiani, this is Richard Crosby.
He's playing Vincent.
I'm doing my scenes with you?
Nice to meet you, Joey.
Wow, I can't believe this.
This is incredible.
I mean, you just won an Oscar.
No, I didn't.
I think you did.
I think I lost three times.
A cookie, would you?
Okay, we're about an hour away from getting
the scene lit.
So, if you guys don't mind, can we
run it a couple of times?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, okay.
All right, let's do it.
And action.
We have to find the rest of the
platoon.
Forget the platoon.
The platoon is gone.
What?
The platoon is dead.
Face facts, Tony.
So, what are we going to do?
We have no reinforcements, no food.
No, we still have food.
In the basement, I saw potatoes and some
dried pasta.
Hang on a minute.
Joey, you keep touching your face.
Is something wrong?
No.
No?
I thought it might be kind of a
cool character thing.
You know, he's a face toucher.
I don't think so.
Let's take it back to Richard's last line.
Action.
We may not have any weapons, but we
still have food.
In the basement, I saw potatoes and some
dried pasta.
And a few tins of tuna.
Tony, we gotta go.
Okay.
Here's a question you never want to have
to ask.
My dad just called and wanted to know
if he could borrow one of your pearl
necklaces.
Did he say what kind of neckline he'd
be wearing?
No.
Well, I've only met him once, but I'm
guessing plunging?
Yeah, he is more of a if you've
got it flaunted kind of father.
I don't have anything like that, but let
me go see if Rachel does.
Yes, include more people in this.
Hey, do you realize that at this time
tomorrow, we're going to be getting married?
Wait a minute, I have a date tomorrow
night.
I just, I can't believe that we made
it.
Well, you don't have to sound so surprised.
I'm sorry, but nothing.
What?
Well, honestly, ever since we got engaged, I've
been waiting for something to flip you out.
Honestly, me too.
Really?
Yeah, you know, I keep thinking that something
stupid is going to come up and I'll
go all, well, Chandler.
But nothing has.
I'm so glad.
Thank you so much for staying so calm
during this.
I mean, it's really, it's made me stay
calm.
I could have been worse.
I'll be right down.
Hi, if you're calling before Saturday, you've reached
Monica and Chandler.
But if you're calling after Saturday, you've reached
Mr. and Mrs. Bing.
Please leave a message for the Bings.
Hey, Maureen.
Hi.
Gosh.
Chandler, this is my cousin Maureen.
We're the Bings.
Hi.
Oh, you guys look so beautiful.
Mr. and Mrs. Bing.
Wow, Monica.
Hey, just so you know, I had my
older brother talk with Chandler.
What is that?
Well, I told him that if he ever
hurt you, I would hunt him down and
kick his ass.
What?
What is the matter with everybody?
I'm serious.
I would kick his ass.
Drugs, please.
My makeup.
Hi.
Chandler.
Mom, thanks for wearing something.
Oh, honey, this is so exciting.
I thought we'd screwed you up so bad
this day would never come.
Oh, I just think soon there'll be lots
of little Bings.
I think we'll have to go back to
work after this and get spit on again.
Well, you're lucky.
At least the people that spit on you
are famous.
Who spits on you?
I don't want to talk about work.
Mrs. Bing, here.
These are my parents, Judy and Jack Ellard.
It's lovely to meet you.
So, are you his mother or his father?
Jack!
What?
I've never seen one before.
There's Ross.
Why don't you go talk to him?
I didn't even have a chance to act
as though I'm okay with it.
Hello, all.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, Mr. Bing.
Nora.
Charles.
It's so great to see you both here.
Yes, although I think we may be seeing
a little too much of some people.
Aren't you a little old to be wearing
a dress like that?
Don't you have a little too much penis
to be wearing a dress like that?
Oh, my God.
Of course you can kick his ass, son.
You can kick anyone's ass you want to.
Thanks, you guys.
Rach, Rach.
Hey, could you do me a favor and
would you talk to Chandler's dad and try
to keep him away from Chandler's mom?
Yeah, but I don't know what he looks
like.
He is the man in the black dress.
Man in the...
Hi.
I'm Rachel.
I'm a friend of Monica and Chandler's.
I'm Amanda.
Oh, I get it.
A-man-da.
Can I have everyone's attention, please?
I'm, uh, I'm Ross Geller.
Dr. Ross Geller.
Dad.
Dad, please.
As I was saying, um, I'm Dr. Ross
Geller.
Uh, and I'm the best man.
And, uh, I have to say I'm, uh,
I'm a little surprised we're all here today.
For those of you who don't know Chandler,
um, he's not the biggest fan of relationships.
In fact, I think, uh, before he met
Monica, the only real relationship he had was
with a girl named Molly.
And he would have married her, only, uh,
she couldn't control her bladder.
It was his dog.
Did I say it was his dog?
Anyway, um, this marriage, uh, is doubly special
for me.
Uh, because not only is the groom my
best friend, but, uh, the bride is my
little sister.
And she's the greatest sister a guy could
ask for.
So if you'd all please join me in
raising a glass to the, the couple we're
here to celebrate.
To the Bings.
How cool is it that the next time
you see Chandler, you're gonna be walking down
the aisle?
Oh, I can't believe that after tomorrow, it's
all gonna be over.
Oh, honey, it's not gonna be over.
You're gonna be married to Chandler.
Yeah.
Oh, maybe I can wear the dress for
Halloween.
All right, I'm gonna go steam my wedding
dress, okay?
Who wants responsibility of making sure nothing happens
to it?
I'll do it.
Who wants it?
Anybody?
I said I'll do it.
Nobody wants to do it?
All right, I'll do it myself.
Oh, I'm not gonna screw it up.
Yeah, you're right, I'm sorry.
Actually, you were a big help tonight.
Yeah, and thanks for putting my grandmother in
the cab and making sure she got to
the hotel safely.
Well, of course, that is what I'm here
for.
Okay, sorry.
Shh.
What grandmother?
Hey, where have you been?
Oh, taking my parents back to the hotel.
Oh.
What, are you going back to work?
Yeah.
Nice shades.
Thanks.
Yeah, I figure if I wear these in
my scenes, at least I won't get spit
in my eyes.
And if I remember correctly, Ray-Ban was
the official sponsor of World War I.
Great.
I'll see you later.
All right.
Hey, where's Chandler?
I think he's in Rachel's room.
See ya.
Chandler.
Chandler?
Hey.
Hi.
Is Monica here?
She's steaming her dress, why?
What's up?
I think Chandler is gone.
What?
He left that.
Tell Monica I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
What's up?
Tell Monica I'm sorry.
Tell her yourself.
Oh, my God.
Chandler just left, though?
Yeah, but maybe it's not what we think.
Maybe it's, Tell Monica I'm sorry, I drank
the last of the milk.
Or, Tell Monica I'm sorry, I used your
tweezer to pluck my nose hair.
He does that, I've seen him.
Or, no, maybe, maybe he was writing to
tell her that he's changed his name.
You know, Tell Monica I'm sorry.
I think it means he freaked out and
left.
Don't be so negative.
Oh, God, isn't it possible that sorry is
sitting in there right now?
Okay, Phoebe, I think Ross is right.
What are we gonna do?
Look, okay, I'm just gonna, I'm gonna have
to go find him and bring him back,
okay?
You make sure Monica does not find out,
Okay, but if you don't find him and
bring him back, I am gonna hunt you
down and kick your ass.
I will find him.
Well, the dress is done.
What?
We're just so happy for you.
Aw, that's so sweet.
Hey, can we just take a minute and
talk about the man that I'm gonna marry
tomorrow?
I mean, how lucky am I?
Hey, that's a good question.
I just hope that someday you guys find
someone like Chandler.
I hope we find someone exactly like Chandler
and soon.
Hey, Joey, can you, uh, go through these
lines with me?
Oh, man, they, they just redid my makeup.
Hey, just the last two pages.
All right.
I found the picture.
Picture?
What picture?
The picture of my wife I'd found in
your pack.
Could you, uh, could you level the script?
I don't want to.
Well, well, I need to see your face
so I can, um, play off your reaction.
Okay, look, um, I know you're this great
actor and you play all those Shakespeare guys
and stuff, but you're spitting all over me.
You're spitting all over me, man.
Well, of course I am.
You know you've been spitting on me?
That's what real actors do.
Annunciation is the mark of a good actor.
And when you enunciate, you spit.
Wow.
Didn't know that.
Hey, thanks.
Okay, okay, check it out.
Picture?
What picture?
Okay.
Doctor, have you, uh, have you seen Chandler?
No, no, I haven't seen him.
Oh, damn.
He's getting married tomorrow, right?
Yes, yes, don't worry.
Everything's fine.
We'll, uh, we'll see you tomorrow at the
wedding.
I wasn't invited.
Well, then we'll, we'll see you the day
after tomorrow.
Mom?
Dad?
What, what, what are you guys doing here?
Well, you kids talk about this place so
much, we thought we'd see what the fuss
is all about.
I certainly see why the girls like coming
here.
Why?
The sexy blonde behind the counter.
Gunther?
Your mother just added him to her list.
What in your list?
Well, the list that, uh, people were allowed
to sleep.
Yes, no, no, I know, I know what
the list is.
Come on, sit down.
Have a cup of joe.
No, I...
No, Dad, I, I, I can't.
I'm sorry.
If you see Chandler, could you just tell
him that I'm looking for him?
And if you see Rita Moreno, let her
know I'm looking for her.
Action.
I found the picture.
What picture?
A picture of my wife in your pack.
You went through my personal property.
Why do you have a picture of Pauline
in your pack?
Because, Vincent, we were lovers for two years.
Wonderful.
Great scene, huh?
You're awesome, man.
And that last speech, you soaked me.
Here's your call sheet for tomorrow.
Oh, I'm not working tomorrow.
You are now.
Oh, no, I can't.
You got to get me out of it.
I have plans.
Important plans!
Ralph said there's still no word from Chandler.
Oh, man.
Oh, but he did say that they found
the grandmother wandering down Fifth Avenue.
Okay, well, there's one down.
I'm getting married today!
Oh!
I think I just cracked a rib.
But I don't care because today is my
wedding day!
My day is finally here!
You know, she might not even notice he's
gone.
Oh, so I'm getting ready!
Oh, my God!
We can't let her start getting ready!
This is too awful!
Shh!
Oh, God!
But wait!
She'll be in the gown and then he
won't show up and then she's going to
have to take off the gown.
Shh!
Stop it, stop it, Rachel.
You can't do this here.
I'm sorry.
It's just so sad.
You've got to pull yourself together.
Monica can't see you like this.
Then she'll know something's wrong.
I know, I know.
Oh, God.
There's no tissue.
Can you grab me some toilet paper?
Yeah.
Oh, that's gone, too.
This is Monica's bathroom, right?
Oh.
Oh, no.
I found one.
Oh, okay.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, God.
Can I have another one?
Sure.
Do you need some floss?
I just cannot imagine what is going to
happen if Chandler doesn't show up.
Oh, here's a whole bunch.
Oh.
I mean, she's going to be at the
wedding waiting for him and people will be
whispering, oh, that poor girl.
You know, and then she'll have to come
back here and live all alone.
Oh, my God.
What?
There was a pregnancy test in the garbage
and it's positive.
Monica's pregnant.
So, I guess she won't be totally alone.
Oh, my God.
I know.
Monica's going to have a baby.
Hey, can this count as her something new?
Oh, my God.
Hey, do you think this is why Chandler
took off?
No, she had to have just taken that
test because I told her I took out
the trash last night.
Oh, God.
This is turning into the worst wedding day
ever.
The bride is pregnant, the groom is missing,
and I'm still holding this.
Okay, Phoebe, we cannot tell anyone about this.
Right.
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, wait, do you know what kind of
birth control she was using?
No.
Why?
Just for the future.
This is hardly a commercial for it.
Anything?
No.
I talked to Joey on the set.
He hasn't heard from him.
I talked to Chandler's parents again.
You told them he was missing?
No.
I made it seem like I was just
calling to chat.
Pretty sure they both think I'm interested in
that.
All right, we've got to tell her that
he's gone.
No, hey, hey, we can't.
Ross, she's going to start getting ready soon.
Well, can't you at least stall her a
little?
I'll go back to some of the places
I went last night.
All right, well, how much time do you
need?
Well, how much time before she absolutely has
to start getting ready?
One hour.
Give me two.
Then why do you ask?
Okay, wish me luck.
Okay, I'm going with you.
Why?
Ross, you're tired.
You've been looking all night and clearly you
suck at this.
I have documented night blindness.
No, you don't.
Okay, but I don't suck.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
Okay, wait, do you know how you're going
to stall her?
Because she is insane about her schedule today.
I don't know.
I'll figure something out.
All right, good luck.
Hey.
Okay, so I thought we'd start with my
makeup and then do my hair.
Okay, uh, but before you do that, I
need you to talk to me.
About what?
Um...
I'm never going to get married!
You will?
The right guy's just around the corner.
Okay, are we done with that?
No, Monica, I'm serious.
Oh, maybe I should just forget about it.
Become a lesbian or something.
Any woman would be lucky to have you.
Well, maybe it would make me feel better
if I slept with Joey.
Rachel, are you okay?
Excuse me, Erin?
Hi, um, I have a little problem with
the schedule.
See, originally, I wasn't supposed to work today,
and I have this wedding that I really
have to be at.
It's my best friend's, and I'm officiating, so
I really can't work past four.
Wow, Joey, you've got to stay until the
end.
We can't stop filming just for you.
It's not like it's your wedding.
It is my wedding.
Did I not make that clear?
But you said your best friend was getting
married.
Yeah, to me.
Yeah, I'm marrying my best friend.
Isn't that beautiful?
But you said you were officiating.
Yeah.
Your own wedding.
Happens more than you think.
I'm sorry, Joey.
It's still no.
I'm having surgery.
What?
Yeah, I just made up the stuff about
the wedding because I didn't want you to
worry about me, but I'm having surgery today.
What kind of surgery?
Transplant.
But you're supposed to work on Monday.
Hair transplant.
But you're not bald.
It's not on my head.
Look, Joey, there's nothing I can do.
Besides, you're probably gonna be out by four
anyway.
We've just got one short scene.
It's just you and Richard, and God knows
he's a pro.
You'll be fine.
Morning, Richard.
Hey, you're here.
Great, great, great.
Let's get going, buddy.
We got a scene to shoot.
I'm wearing two belts.
Are you drunk?
No.
Yes, you are.
We're never gonna find him.
He's one guy in a huge city.
Oh, my God.
Is that him?
That is an old Chinese woman.
He could be in disguise, you know.
You know what?
You know, you're right.
You're absolutely right.
Wait a minute.
Chandler.
Now you're thinking.
You know, maybe we're just approaching this all
wrong.
If you're Chandler and you want to hide,
where is the last place on Earth people
would think you'd go?
So this is your office.
Where'd you guys find me?
I knew I should've hid at the gym.
What the hell are you doing?
Panicking.
And using the Internet to try to prove
that I'm related to Monica.
How is she?
She's fine.
She doesn't know you're gone.
And she doesn't have to know.
Okay?
Now, come on.
We're going home.
No, no, no.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Because if I go home, we're gonna become
the Bings.
I can't be the Bings.
What's wrong with being the Bings?
The Bings have horrible marriages.
They yell, they fight, and they use the
pool boy as a pawn in their sexual
games.
Chandler, have you ever put on a black
cocktail dress and asked me up to your
hotel room?
No.
Then you are neither of your parents.
It's not just their marriage.
I mean, look at yours.
Look at everybody's.
The only person that can make marriage work
is Paul Newman.
And I've met me.
I am no Paul Newman.
I don't race cars.
I don't make popcorn.
None of my proceeds go to charity.
But look, Chandler.
Right now, no one has a lower opinion
of you than I do.
But I totally believe you can do this.
I want to.
I love her so much.
But I'm afraid...
This is too huge.
You know, okay.
You're right.
It is huge.
So why don't we take it just a
little bit at a time.
Okay?
Um, forget getting married for a sec.
Just forget about it.
Can you just come home and take a
shower?
Well, yeah, but then...
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba!